The world was burning The lies were loud. We were
the joking tabloid crowd.
We had no shelter. We had no home. Just the open
road and a telephone. But you.
You built a fortress. You gave us walls when we
were torn. You built a place to hide from the
storm. You are the iron hand. You are the shield.
The only army that would not yield. This is our
fortress.
This isn't LA. This isn't a dream. This is a
warehouse. This is a scream. We're building our
truth. We're building our sound. Right here on
our hallowed ground. God is yellow.
You built a fortress. You gave us walls when we
were torn. You built a place to hide from the
storm. You are the iron head. You are the shield.
The only army that would not yield. This is our
fortress.
Our fortress,
our home
We are the fortress